[{"subjectID":"hetbx6o4d1","prolificID":"67047ee9910a4dfe0c338eb7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742159e656488da374530a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664145738,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"176","question":"What is your strategy for eating a really messy taco?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":51,"rt":25814,"timeElapsed":96342},{"subjectID":"hetbx6o4d1","prolificID":"67047ee9910a4dfe0c338eb7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742159e656488da374530a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664159278,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"176","question":"What is your strategy for eating a really messy taco?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":13539,"timeElapsed":109883},{"subjectID":"hetbx6o4d1","prolificID":"67047ee9910a4dfe0c338eb7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742159e656488da374530a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664166437,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"176","question":"What is your strategy for eating a really messy taco?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":7155,"timeElapsed":117042},{"subjectID":"hetbx6o4d1","prolificID":"67047ee9910a4dfe0c338eb7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742159e656488da374530a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664173093,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"176","question":"What is your strategy for eating a really messy taco?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":6652,"timeElapsed":123698},{"subjectID":"hetbx6o4d1","prolificID":"67047ee9910a4dfe0c338eb7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742159e656488da374530a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664178040,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"176","question":"What is your strategy for eating a really messy taco?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":4943,"timeElapsed":128645},{"subjectID":"hetbx6o4d1","prolificID":"67047ee9910a4dfe0c338eb7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742159e656488da374530a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664187795,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"176","question":"What is your strategy for eating a really messy taco?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":9752,"timeElapsed":138400},{"subjectID":"hetbx6o4d1","prolificID":"67047ee9910a4dfe0c338eb7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742159e656488da374530a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664195123,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"176","question":"What is your strategy for eating a really messy taco?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":7325,"timeElapsed":145728},{"subjectID":"hetbx6o4d1","prolificID":"67047ee9910a4dfe0c338eb7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742159e656488da374530a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664202150,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"176","question":"What is your strategy for eating a really messy taco?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":7023,"timeElapsed":152755},{"subjectID":"hetbx6o4d1","prolificID":"67047ee9910a4dfe0c338eb7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742159e656488da374530a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664207090,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"176","question":"What is your strategy for eating a really messy taco?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":4936,"timeElapsed":157695},{"subjectID":"hetbx6o4d1","prolificID":"67047ee9910a4dfe0c338eb7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742159e656488da374530a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664219315,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"54","question":"Do you believe in the death penalty? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":9952,"timeElapsed":169920},{"subjectID":"hetbx6o4d1","prolificID":"67047ee9910a4dfe0c338eb7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742159e656488da374530a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664224681,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"54","question":"Do you believe in the death penalty? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":5363,"timeElapsed":175286},{"subjectID":"hetbx6o4d1","prolificID":"67047ee9910a4dfe0c338eb7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742159e656488da374530a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664231067,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"54","question":"Do you believe in the death penalty? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":6383,"timeElapsed":181671},{"subjectID":"hetbx6o4d1","prolificID":"67047ee9910a4dfe0c338eb7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742159e656488da374530a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664234523,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"54","question":"Do you believe in the death penalty? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":3453,"timeElapsed":185128},{"subjectID":"hetbx6o4d1","prolificID":"67047ee9910a4dfe0c338eb7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742159e656488da374530a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664238961,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"54","question":"Do you believe in the death penalty? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":4434,"timeElapsed":189566},{"subjectID":"hetbx6o4d1","prolificID":"67047ee9910a4dfe0c338eb7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742159e656488da374530a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664244956,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"54","question":"Do you believe in the death penalty? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":5993,"timeElapsed":195561},{"subjectID":"hetbx6o4d1","prolificID":"67047ee9910a4dfe0c338eb7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742159e656488da374530a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664248908,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"54","question":"Do you believe in the death penalty? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":3949,"timeElapsed":199513},{"subjectID":"hetbx6o4d1","prolificID":"67047ee9910a4dfe0c338eb7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742159e656488da374530a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664252986,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"54","question":"Do you believe in the death penalty? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":48,"rt":4075,"timeElapsed":203591},{"subjectID":"hetbx6o4d1","prolificID":"67047ee9910a4dfe0c338eb7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742159e656488da374530a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664256093,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"54","question":"Do you believe in the death penalty? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":45,"rt":3104,"timeElapsed":206698},{"subjectID":"hetbx6o4d1","prolificID":"67047ee9910a4dfe0c338eb7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742159e656488da374530a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664266512,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"158","question":"Where did you go to high school? What was your high school like?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":8637,"timeElapsed":217117},{"subjectID":"hetbx6o4d1","prolificID":"67047ee9910a4dfe0c338eb7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742159e656488da374530a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664269799,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"158","question":"Where did you go to high school? What was your high school like?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":3284,"timeElapsed":220404},{"subjectID":"hetbx6o4d1","prolificID":"67047ee9910a4dfe0c338eb7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742159e656488da374530a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664273833,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"158","question":"Where did you go to high school? What was your high school like?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":4031,"timeElapsed":224438},{"subjectID":"hetbx6o4d1","prolificID":"67047ee9910a4dfe0c338eb7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742159e656488da374530a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664276832,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"158","question":"Where did you go to high school? What was your high school like?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":2997,"timeElapsed":227437},{"subjectID":"hetbx6o4d1","prolificID":"67047ee9910a4dfe0c338eb7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742159e656488da374530a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664279563,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"158","question":"Where did you go to high school? What was your high school like?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":2728,"timeElapsed":230168},{"subjectID":"hetbx6o4d1","prolificID":"67047ee9910a4dfe0c338eb7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742159e656488da374530a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664284904,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"158","question":"Where did you go to high school? What was your high school like?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":5338,"timeElapsed":235509},{"subjectID":"hetbx6o4d1","prolificID":"67047ee9910a4dfe0c338eb7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742159e656488da374530a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664288274,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"158","question":"Where did you go to high school? What was your high school like?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":3366,"timeElapsed":238879},{"subjectID":"hetbx6o4d1","prolificID":"67047ee9910a4dfe0c338eb7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742159e656488da374530a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664291252,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"158","question":"Where did you go to high school? What was your high school like?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":2975,"timeElapsed":241857},{"subjectID":"hetbx6o4d1","prolificID":"67047ee9910a4dfe0c338eb7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742159e656488da374530a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664293985,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"158","question":"Where did you go to high school? What was your high school like?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":2730,"timeElapsed":244590},{"subjectID":"hetbx6o4d1","prolificID":"67047ee9910a4dfe0c338eb7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742159e656488da374530a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664299583,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Where did you go to high school? What was your high school like?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":5595,"timeElapsed":250188},{"subjectID":"hetbx6o4d1","prolificID":"67047ee9910a4dfe0c338eb7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742159e656488da374530a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664314372,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"105","question":"Do you want to have kids? If you already do, did you want kids before having them? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":13486,"timeElapsed":264976},{"subjectID":"hetbx6o4d1","prolificID":"67047ee9910a4dfe0c338eb7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742159e656488da374530a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664316608,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"105","question":"Do you want to have kids? If you already do, did you want kids before having them? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":2233,"timeElapsed":267213},{"subjectID":"hetbx6o4d1","prolificID":"67047ee9910a4dfe0c338eb7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742159e656488da374530a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664319508,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"105","question":"Do you want to have kids? If you already do, did you want kids before having them? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2897,"timeElapsed":270113},{"subjectID":"hetbx6o4d1","prolificID":"67047ee9910a4dfe0c338eb7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742159e656488da374530a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664321999,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"105","question":"Do you want to have kids? If you already do, did you want kids before having them? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2488,"timeElapsed":272604},{"subjectID":"hetbx6o4d1","prolificID":"67047ee9910a4dfe0c338eb7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742159e656488da374530a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664327163,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"105","question":"Do you want to have kids? If you already do, did you want kids before having them? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":5161,"timeElapsed":277768},{"subjectID":"hetbx6o4d1","prolificID":"67047ee9910a4dfe0c338eb7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742159e656488da374530a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664330430,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"105","question":"Do you want to have kids? If you already do, did you want kids before having them? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":3264,"timeElapsed":281035},{"subjectID":"hetbx6o4d1","prolificID":"67047ee9910a4dfe0c338eb7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742159e656488da374530a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664332884,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"105","question":"Do you want to have kids? If you already do, did you want kids before having them? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":2451,"timeElapsed":283489},{"subjectID":"hetbx6o4d1","prolificID":"67047ee9910a4dfe0c338eb7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742159e656488da374530a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664335874,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"105","question":"Do you want to have kids? If you already do, did you want kids before having them? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":2988,"timeElapsed":286479},{"subjectID":"hetbx6o4d1","prolificID":"67047ee9910a4dfe0c338eb7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742159e656488da374530a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664338997,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"105","question":"Do you want to have kids? If you already do, did you want kids before having them? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":3120,"timeElapsed":289602},{"subjectID":"hetbx6o4d1","prolificID":"67047ee9910a4dfe0c338eb7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742159e656488da374530a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664389578,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"25","question":"Complete this sentence: I wish I had someone with whom I could share…","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":46608,"timeElapsed":340183},{"subjectID":"hetbx6o4d1","prolificID":"67047ee9910a4dfe0c338eb7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742159e656488da374530a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664392632,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"25","question":"Complete this sentence: I wish I had someone with whom I could share…","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":3052,"timeElapsed":343237},{"subjectID":"hetbx6o4d1","prolificID":"67047ee9910a4dfe0c338eb7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742159e656488da374530a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664395307,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"25","question":"Complete this sentence: I wish I had someone with whom I could share…","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":2672,"timeElapsed":345912},{"subjectID":"hetbx6o4d1","prolificID":"67047ee9910a4dfe0c338eb7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742159e656488da374530a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664397782,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"25","question":"Complete this sentence: I wish I had someone with whom I could share…","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":2472,"timeElapsed":348387},{"subjectID":"hetbx6o4d1","prolificID":"67047ee9910a4dfe0c338eb7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742159e656488da374530a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664400384,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"25","question":"Complete this sentence: I wish I had someone with whom I could share…","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":2599,"timeElapsed":350989},{"subjectID":"hetbx6o4d1","prolificID":"67047ee9910a4dfe0c338eb7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742159e656488da374530a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664404729,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"25","question":"Complete this sentence: I wish I had someone with whom I could share…","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":4343,"timeElapsed":355334},{"subjectID":"hetbx6o4d1","prolificID":"67047ee9910a4dfe0c338eb7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742159e656488da374530a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664406976,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"25","question":"Complete this sentence: I wish I had someone with whom I could share…","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":2243,"timeElapsed":357581},{"subjectID":"hetbx6o4d1","prolificID":"67047ee9910a4dfe0c338eb7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742159e656488da374530a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664409916,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"25","question":"Complete this sentence: I wish I had someone with whom I could share…","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":2938,"timeElapsed":360521},{"subjectID":"hetbx6o4d1","prolificID":"67047ee9910a4dfe0c338eb7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742159e656488da374530a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664412817,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"25","question":"Complete this sentence: I wish I had someone with whom I could share…","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":2898,"timeElapsed":363422},{"subjectID":"hetbx6o4d1","prolificID":"67047ee9910a4dfe0c338eb7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742159e656488da374530a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664423262,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"79","question":"What famous person do you think you would be great friends with if you met?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":9227,"timeElapsed":373867},{"subjectID":"hetbx6o4d1","prolificID":"67047ee9910a4dfe0c338eb7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742159e656488da374530a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664426098,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"79","question":"What famous person do you think you would be great friends with if you met?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":2833,"timeElapsed":376703},{"subjectID":"hetbx6o4d1","prolificID":"67047ee9910a4dfe0c338eb7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742159e656488da374530a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664429416,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"79","question":"What famous person do you think you would be great friends with if you met?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":3315,"timeElapsed":380021},{"subjectID":"hetbx6o4d1","prolificID":"67047ee9910a4dfe0c338eb7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742159e656488da374530a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664432756,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"79","question":"What famous person do you think you would be great friends with if you met?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":3338,"timeElapsed":383361},{"subjectID":"hetbx6o4d1","prolificID":"67047ee9910a4dfe0c338eb7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742159e656488da374530a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664435629,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"79","question":"What famous person do you think you would be great friends with if you met?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":2871,"timeElapsed":386234},{"subjectID":"hetbx6o4d1","prolificID":"67047ee9910a4dfe0c338eb7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742159e656488da374530a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664440926,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"79","question":"What famous person do you think you would be great friends with if you met?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":5294,"timeElapsed":391531},{"subjectID":"hetbx6o4d1","prolificID":"67047ee9910a4dfe0c338eb7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742159e656488da374530a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664443753,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"79","question":"What famous person do you think you would be great friends with if you met?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":2824,"timeElapsed":394358},{"subjectID":"hetbx6o4d1","prolificID":"67047ee9910a4dfe0c338eb7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742159e656488da374530a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664447477,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"79","question":"What famous person do you think you would be great friends with if you met?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":3721,"timeElapsed":398082},{"subjectID":"hetbx6o4d1","prolificID":"67047ee9910a4dfe0c338eb7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742159e656488da374530a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664449810,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"79","question":"What famous person do you think you would be great friends with if you met?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":2330,"timeElapsed":400414},{"subjectID":"hetbx6o4d1","prolificID":"67047ee9910a4dfe0c338eb7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742159e656488da374530a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664459494,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":8418,"timeElapsed":410099},{"subjectID":"hetbx6o4d1","prolificID":"67047ee9910a4dfe0c338eb7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742159e656488da374530a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664474507,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":15010,"timeElapsed":425112},{"subjectID":"hetbx6o4d1","prolificID":"67047ee9910a4dfe0c338eb7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742159e656488da374530a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664481923,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":7413,"timeElapsed":432528},{"subjectID":"hetbx6o4d1","prolificID":"67047ee9910a4dfe0c338eb7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742159e656488da374530a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664486566,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":4640,"timeElapsed":437171},{"subjectID":"hetbx6o4d1","prolificID":"67047ee9910a4dfe0c338eb7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742159e656488da374530a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664490072,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":3503,"timeElapsed":440677},{"subjectID":"hetbx6o4d1","prolificID":"67047ee9910a4dfe0c338eb7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742159e656488da374530a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664492336,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":2260,"timeElapsed":442941},{"subjectID":"hetbx6o4d1","prolificID":"67047ee9910a4dfe0c338eb7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742159e656488da374530a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664497274,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":4935,"timeElapsed":447878},{"subjectID":"hetbx6o4d1","prolificID":"67047ee9910a4dfe0c338eb7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742159e656488da374530a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664499132,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":1854,"timeElapsed":449736},{"subjectID":"hetbx6o4d1","prolificID":"67047ee9910a4dfe0c338eb7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742159e656488da374530a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664501382,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":2247,"timeElapsed":451987},{"subjectID":"hetbx6o4d1","prolificID":"67047ee9910a4dfe0c338eb7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742159e656488da374530a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664504181,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":2796,"timeElapsed":454786},{"subjectID":"hetbx6o4d1","prolificID":"67047ee9910a4dfe0c338eb7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742159e656488da374530a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664513438,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"162","question":"How often do you get your hair cut? Where do you go? Have you ever had a really bad haircut experience?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":7607,"timeElapsed":464043},{"subjectID":"hetbx6o4d1","prolificID":"67047ee9910a4dfe0c338eb7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742159e656488da374530a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664515208,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"162","question":"How often do you get your hair cut? Where do you go? Have you ever had a really bad haircut experience?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":1766,"timeElapsed":465813},{"subjectID":"hetbx6o4d1","prolificID":"67047ee9910a4dfe0c338eb7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742159e656488da374530a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664517383,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"162","question":"How often do you get your hair cut? Where do you go? Have you ever had a really bad haircut experience?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":2171,"timeElapsed":467988},{"subjectID":"hetbx6o4d1","prolificID":"67047ee9910a4dfe0c338eb7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742159e656488da374530a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664520313,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"162","question":"How often do you get your hair cut? Where do you go? Have you ever had a really bad haircut experience?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":2927,"timeElapsed":470918},{"subjectID":"hetbx6o4d1","prolificID":"67047ee9910a4dfe0c338eb7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742159e656488da374530a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664522511,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"162","question":"How often do you get your hair cut? Where do you go? Have you ever had a really bad haircut experience?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":2195,"timeElapsed":473115},{"subjectID":"hetbx6o4d1","prolificID":"67047ee9910a4dfe0c338eb7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742159e656488da374530a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664526548,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"162","question":"How often do you get your hair cut? Where do you go? Have you ever had a really bad haircut experience?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":4035,"timeElapsed":477153},{"subjectID":"hetbx6o4d1","prolificID":"67047ee9910a4dfe0c338eb7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742159e656488da374530a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664528504,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"162","question":"How often do you get your hair cut? Where do you go? Have you ever had a really bad haircut experience?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":1953,"timeElapsed":479109},{"subjectID":"hetbx6o4d1","prolificID":"67047ee9910a4dfe0c338eb7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742159e656488da374530a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664531961,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"162","question":"How often do you get your hair cut? Where do you go? Have you ever had a really bad haircut experience?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":3456,"timeElapsed":482566},{"subjectID":"hetbx6o4d1","prolificID":"67047ee9910a4dfe0c338eb7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742159e656488da374530a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664534270,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"162","question":"How often do you get your hair cut? Where do you go? Have you ever had a really bad haircut experience?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":2307,"timeElapsed":484875},{"subjectID":"hetbx6o4d1","prolificID":"67047ee9910a4dfe0c338eb7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742159e656488da374530a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664543499,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"81","question":"In general, do you wish people were MORE or LESS serious? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":8118,"timeElapsed":494104},{"subjectID":"hetbx6o4d1","prolificID":"67047ee9910a4dfe0c338eb7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742159e656488da374530a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664548133,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"81","question":"In general, do you wish people were MORE or LESS serious? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":4633,"timeElapsed":498738},{"subjectID":"hetbx6o4d1","prolificID":"67047ee9910a4dfe0c338eb7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742159e656488da374530a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664556323,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"81","question":"In general, do you wish people were MORE or LESS serious? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":8187,"timeElapsed":506928},{"subjectID":"hetbx6o4d1","prolificID":"67047ee9910a4dfe0c338eb7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742159e656488da374530a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664560334,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"81","question":"In general, do you wish people were MORE or LESS serious? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":4008,"timeElapsed":510939},{"subjectID":"hetbx6o4d1","prolificID":"67047ee9910a4dfe0c338eb7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742159e656488da374530a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664562585,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"81","question":"In general, do you wish people were MORE or LESS serious? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":2248,"timeElapsed":513190},{"subjectID":"hetbx6o4d1","prolificID":"67047ee9910a4dfe0c338eb7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742159e656488da374530a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664568500,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"81","question":"In general, do you wish people were MORE or LESS serious? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":5912,"timeElapsed":519105},{"subjectID":"hetbx6o4d1","prolificID":"67047ee9910a4dfe0c338eb7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742159e656488da374530a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664570741,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"81","question":"In general, do you wish people were MORE or LESS serious? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":2239,"timeElapsed":521346},{"subjectID":"hetbx6o4d1","prolificID":"67047ee9910a4dfe0c338eb7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742159e656488da374530a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664573143,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"81","question":"In general, do you wish people were MORE or LESS serious? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":2398,"timeElapsed":523748},{"subjectID":"hetbx6o4d1","prolificID":"67047ee9910a4dfe0c338eb7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742159e656488da374530a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664575936,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"81","question":"In general, do you wish people were MORE or LESS serious? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":2790,"timeElapsed":526541},{"subjectID":"hetbx6o4d1","prolificID":"67047ee9910a4dfe0c338eb7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742159e656488da374530a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664590696,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"198","question":"Do you know any “party tricks”? If so, describe them. If not, describe one you would like to learn.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":12669,"timeElapsed":541301},{"subjectID":"hetbx6o4d1","prolificID":"67047ee9910a4dfe0c338eb7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742159e656488da374530a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664596971,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"198","question":"Do you know any “party tricks”? If so, describe them. If not, describe one you would like to learn.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":45,"rt":6273,"timeElapsed":547576},{"subjectID":"hetbx6o4d1","prolificID":"67047ee9910a4dfe0c338eb7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742159e656488da374530a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664599809,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"198","question":"Do you know any “party tricks”? If so, describe them. If not, describe one you would like to learn.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":2835,"timeElapsed":550414},{"subjectID":"hetbx6o4d1","prolificID":"67047ee9910a4dfe0c338eb7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742159e656488da374530a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664605038,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"198","question":"Do you know any “party tricks”? If so, describe them. If not, describe one you would like to learn.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":5227,"timeElapsed":555643},{"subjectID":"hetbx6o4d1","prolificID":"67047ee9910a4dfe0c338eb7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742159e656488da374530a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664607619,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"198","question":"Do you know any “party tricks”? If so, describe them. If not, describe one you would like to learn.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":2578,"timeElapsed":558224},{"subjectID":"hetbx6o4d1","prolificID":"67047ee9910a4dfe0c338eb7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742159e656488da374530a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664611883,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"198","question":"Do you know any “party tricks”? If so, describe them. If not, describe one you would like to learn.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":51,"rt":4261,"timeElapsed":562488},{"subjectID":"hetbx6o4d1","prolificID":"67047ee9910a4dfe0c338eb7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742159e656488da374530a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664613583,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"198","question":"Do you know any “party tricks”? If so, describe them. If not, describe one you would like to learn.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":1697,"timeElapsed":564187},{"subjectID":"hetbx6o4d1","prolificID":"67047ee9910a4dfe0c338eb7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742159e656488da374530a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664616830,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"198","question":"Do you know any “party tricks”? If so, describe them. If not, describe one you would like to learn.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":3244,"timeElapsed":567435},{"subjectID":"hetbx6o4d1","prolificID":"67047ee9910a4dfe0c338eb7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742159e656488da374530a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664619462,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"198","question":"Do you know any “party tricks”? If so, describe them. If not, describe one you would like to learn.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":51,"rt":2629,"timeElapsed":570067}]